

cepian_tapu21@student.sust .edu

+8801515245537

9

Dhaka, Bangladesh

in

linkedin.com/in/tapasri-bb6450a194

SKILLS

Macro Photography

Microsoft Office

MATLAB

Creating Ads

Adobe Photoshop

Video Editing

LANGUAGES

Bangla

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

English

Professional Working Proficiency

Hind

Professional Working Proficiency

Spanish

Elementary Proficiency

INTERESTS

Volunteering

Music

Traveling

Maths

Tapasri Barua

Chemical Engineer

I am a trustworthy person who is great at time management, always enthusiastic, willing to learn new skills and try to improve previous skills. I have completed my research work on the blending of conventional polymers with poly-lactic acid. Currently, I am searching for a job in a reputed company that will bring my knowledge to use as a chemical engineer.

EDUCATION

Chemical Engineering and Polymer Science

Shahjalal University of Science and Technology

02/2016 - 02/2021

Higher Secondary School Certificate

St. Joseph Higher Secondary School

02/2014 - 06/2015 Dhaka, Bangladesh

Sylhet, Bangladesh

Sylhet

Sylhet

WORK EXPERIENCE

Research Assistant

Shahjalal University of Science and Technology

08/2019 - 08/2020

Research Project

Polylactic acid blending with conventional polymer: extend of properties improvement

Volunteer

Unicef

02/2020 - 08/2020

Tasks

Measles-Rubella Campaign 2020

TRAINING AND WORKSHOP

Training Institute for Chemical Industries (TICI) (06/2019 - 06/2019)

CERTIFICATES

Python Data Structures (Coursera) (08/2020 - 09/2020)

coursera.org/verify/6H6WGJ6QW6TM

Introduction to Python (Coursera) (08/2020 - 09/2020)

coursera.org/verify/BJ7LDJ6Q3C34

CO-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

National Chem-E-Car Competition, BUET 2019 (01/2019 - 01/2019)

Participation

Bangladesh Academy of Sciences (BAS) Olympiad (06/2015 - 06/2015)

Participation

Bangladesh Mathematical Olympiad (BMO) (05/2014 - 05/2014)

Participation